Ajay Ko
[Music]
Hello friends welcome to my
video. I am telling you about a bank failure these days.
This channel opened four
percent higher and
closed at 4.5 percent. So this is a 15-minute
chart. You can see it
is standing here. This close loop, if it was a little
good today, it can go up. A
big candle has formed, so there is a good chance of it going up to here.
If it
can be confirmed, but here it is,
New Delhi and Language 1626 son 1600. It
sticks. Now I will
show you questions and answers in the match.
Look, don't think this channel, this throw means
after entering, the comment cream is
sent here and the middle band is
closing above the middle band, which is a positive indication. The
second one is
also showing in the Bollinger Band. And
after that I will show you
183, since the cloud which you can see in this, the
author is closing above the cloud. Here, a
little bit down, peer back.  If it is closing above
then there is a very good possibility that it
can go above, if it is subscribed then the whole
signal is positive and if this
is Nifty, Singapore Nifty, I will show you
what is the condition of Singapore Nifty, you will get to know
where the market can go,
see this point right now and
our police goes before these robbers
and this can happen to you, that is why they have more, that is,
you can send it further in the picture by rotating it to 1665,
that for this information I will come in front of you
friends, I will not meet you so soon in this video, it had happened